# Sem Plaatsman

hello@semplaatsman.nl \* semplaatsman.nl \* Haarlem, The Netherlands

My name is Sem Plaatsman, a BSc Information Technology student at Inholland University of Applied Sciences in Haarlem. Over the past three years, I have been able to utilize my passion for problem-solving and innovation in various projects and programming languages such as Java, Python, (No)SQL, and React. For example, I have helped develop an AI speech recognition system with a React front-end. My ambition is to further develop my technical skills in CI/CD and Cloud Computing.

### **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Website:semplaatsman.nlEmail:hello@semplaatsman.nlGitHub:github.com/SemPlaatsmanLinkedIn:linkedin.com/in/sem-plaatsman

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

S.P. Abonneeservice 03/2024 - present

**Employee Automation** 

Haarlem, The Netherlands

- Developed an SSO system with performance, security, and unit testing.
- Worked on an AI model that attempts to predict when a subscriber will cancel. This AI model is integrated
  with the existing retention modules.

S.P. Abonneeservice 09/2023 – 01/2024

Development merit
 Developed a JWT-authenticated PWA for S.P.'s customers for statistical information.

- Development Intern Haarlem, The Netherlands
- Collaborated within a multidisciplinary context. Analyzed requirements and translated them technically for stakeholders.
- Gained experience with React, ASP.NET, JWT, TypeScript, SCSS, MySQL, and other technologies.

# **Zegel Retailing (franchisee of Blokker and Intertoys)**

01/2019 - 09/2023

Retail Employee

Texel, The Netherlands

• All-round retail employee focusing on customer-oriented service and operational support.

## **EDUCATION**

# **Inholland University of Applied Sciences**

09/2021 - present

Information Technology full-time | Bachelor

Haarlem, The Netherlands

- In year 2, I helped year 1 students with programming in C# (credit point).
- Successfully completed various multidisciplinary projects with a variety of technologies.
- Obtained propaedeutic diploma in the first year.

### **OSG De Hogeberg**

09/2015 - 07/2021

High School | HAVO

Texel, The Netherlands

- Completed a year-long final research project on AI.
- Became interested in programming during a Python project in the 4th year.

### **SKILLS & INTERESTS**

- **Soft skills:** Solution-oriented, perseverance, and helpfulness.
- Hard skills: OOP languages, (No)SQL, GitHub, Web technologies, AI.
- **Interesses:** Raspberry Pi/Arduino, gym, gaming, cooking, and climbing/bouldering.